Guide to the Trumbull College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 194x-1972 Maintained by the Master
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Trumbull College, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1934-1972 maintained by the master
1930-1986
RU 322
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
5.25
The records consist of student records maintained by the master of Trumbull College, Yale University.
Trumbull College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-N-2 (YRG 13-N-2), Records of the master of Trumbull College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the master of Trumbull College, Yale University.
Biographical / Historical
The title "Master" for chief executive officers of residential colleges was changed to "Head of College" in April of 2016.
College students; Trumbull College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student information on the Classes of 1971 and 1972, Accession 19ND-A-350
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2047
  - Freshman materials Class of 1971, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Freshman room allocations Class of 1971, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class o f 1971 General information and statistics, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1971 data cards
  - Class of 1971 Guideline report, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Freshman materials Class of 1972, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Freshman room allocations Class of 1972, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1972 General Information and statistics, 1968, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Admission data and grade cards, 1930-1963; Accession 2003-A-105
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2033
  Scope and Contents
  Includes correspondence, medical data, police reports, disciplinary files and recommendations.